(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-24T04:30:15.871859",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
水底と 天上の 隙間
In the gap between the depths and the heavens,
見下ろした 三日月も 笑っている
even the crescent moon looking down is smiling.
胡乱な センチメントだって
Even a dubious sentiment
包み隠す ネイビーブルー
is wrapped and hidden in navy blue.
さあ
Now,
夜を あげる
I'll give you the night,
終わらない
an endless...
夜を あげる
I'll give you the night,
さあ
Now,
終わらない
An endless...
夜を あげる
I'll give you the night,
君だけの 夜を あげる
I'll give you a night just for you,
夜を あげる
I'll give you the night,
静寂を 切り裂いた 轟音
The roaring sound that tore through the silence,
幕が 開いていく
the curtain is rising.
声が聞こえてる
I can hear a voice,
聞こえてる
I can hear it,
声が聞こえてる
I can hear a voice
向こうから
from the other side.
頭に響いた アラートを辿って
Following the alert echoing in my head,
今
now
空は騒いでる 騒いでる
the skies are roaring, roaring.
未確認ヒール
An unidentified heel,
ランページ アレグロ背負って駆け出して
rampage, bearing allegro as I run forth—
さあ！
come on!
SOSを SOSを SOSを SOSを…
Chasing SOS, SOS, SOS, SOS...
西北西に 千光年だ もう向かっている 向かっている
One thousand light-years away to the west-northwest, already heading there, heading there.
SOSを SOSを SOSを SOSを…
Chasing SOS, SOS, SOS, SOS...
警報 前方接近中だ さあ歌っていけ 歌っていけ
Alarm, approaching from the front. Come on, keep singing, keep singing.
波に呑まれるな 呑まれるな
Do not get swallowed by the waves,
波に呑まれるな 声を出せ
do not get swallowed, raise your voice.
彼方で光った ポイントに目掛けて
Aiming at the point that shone in the distance,
今
now
空は騒いでる 騒いでる
the skies are roaring, roaring.
規格外ゲノム トランジション
Extraordinary genome transition,
アレグロ背負って負けなしで さあ！
bearing allegro with no losses, come on!
僕の番だ ah
Ah, now it's my turn!
SOSを SOSを SOSを SOSを…
Chasing SOS, SOS, SOS, SOS...
西北西に 千光年だ もう向かっている 向かっている
One thousand light-years away to the west-northwest, already heading there, heading there.
SOSを SOSを SOSを SOSを…
Chasing SOS, SOS, SOS, SOS...
警報 全方位解析中だ さあ歌っていけ 歌っていけ
Alarm, all-around analysis in progress. Come on, keep singing, keep singing.
抗っていけ 笑ったままで 歌っていけ
Keep resisting with a smile, keep singing.
歌っていけ さあ
Keep singing, come on!
皆さん、初めまして！
Hello everyone, nice to meet you!
今日は私たちミッドナイトグランドオーケストラ ファーストライブ「OVERTURE」にご参加いただき、誠にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for joining us today for our Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st Live "OVERTURE"!
誠にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
皆さんありがとうございます！いえい！
Everyone, thank you! Yay!
ミッドナイトグランドオーケストラとは、私、星街すいせとタクトイヌガサキさんが中心となって結成された音楽ユニットで、
Midnight Grand Orchestra is a music unit centered around myself, Hoshimachi Suisei, and Taku Inugasaki,
先月7月27日にですね、デビューミニアルバム「Overture」をビアトイズファクトリーさんからリリースさせていただき、そのメジャーデビュー記念ライブということで、
and last month on July 27th, we released our debut mini-album "Overture" from Toy's Factory. As our major debut commemoration live,
本日この超豪華なミドグラ専用ステージから最高の音楽を皆さんにお届けできたと思っております！
we hope to deliver the absolute best music to everyone from this super luxurious MidGura exclusive stage today!
いや、めちゃくちゃ豪華っすね！
Man, this is super luxurious!
いや、すごいですね！居心地はどうですか？
It really is! How does it feel?
最高です！いえい！
It's the best! Yay!
ということでですね、YouTubeのチラ見せ配信はなんとここまでとなってしまいました！YouTubeの皆さん、大変申し訳ございません！ここでお別れです。
And with that, our YouTube preview stream ends right here! To everyone on YouTube, we are so sorry! This is where we say goodbye.
このライブのね、とてつもない感じが結構伝わったんじゃないかなと思いますので、ぜひね、気になった方はSPWNの方で最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていただけたら嬉しいです！
I think this gave you a good sense of how incredible this live is, so if you're interested, we'd be thrilled if you joined us on SPWN to get hyped all the way to the end!
ぜひぜひよろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
ではね、今日は伝説のライブになること間違いなしなので、ぜひ最後まで見てくださーい！
Well then, today's live is bound to be legendary, so be sure to watch till the very end!
みなさん もっともっと 盛り上がっていきましょう！
Everyone, let's get even more excited!
次のご機嫌なナンバーを聞いてください！
Please listen to our next upbeat number!
アレグロ！
Allegro!